// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let evs = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Rhino found in kaziranga ?",
    answer: "One horned",
    options: [
      "Two horned",
      "One horned",
      "Three horned ",
      "Hornless"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "An eco system consist of ________ ?",
    answer: "Biotic and Abiotic factors",
    options: [
      "Population",
      "Abiotic community",
      "Animal population and no-living elements",
      "Biotic and Abiotic factors"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The word environment is derive from ?",
    answer: "France",
    options: [
      "India",
      "France",
      "Germany",
      "English"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Earth day is celebrated every year on ?",
    answer: "22nd April",
    options: [
      "26th October",
      "25th December",
      "22nd April",
      "31st January"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In India” National Food security Act” was enhanced in the year ?",
    answer: "2013",
    options: [
      "2013",
      "2011",
      "2009",
      "1997"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Noise pollution is measured in ?",
    answer: "Decibel unit",
    options: [
      "Gram",
      "Dobson unit",
      "Hertz",
      "Decibel unit"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Green house gas is _______ ?",
    answer: "Chlorofluorocarbon",
    options: [
      "Oxygen",
      "Chlorofluorocarbon",
      "Chlorine",
      "Chlorobenzene"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The term ‘ecosystem’ was termed by ?",
    answer: "A.G Tansley",
    options: [
      "Ernest Hackle",
      "Aristotle",
      "Hooker",
      "A.G Tansley"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is situ conservation ?",
    answer: "National park",
    options: [
      "Aquarium",
      "National park",
      "Zoo",
      "Botanical Garden"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The chief source of energy in environment is ?",
    answer: "Sun",
    options: [
      "Sun",
      "Human",
      "Animals",
      "Crude Oil"
    ]
  },
];